Information

- +502 59539872
- ≥ alv.diego19@gmail.com

Soft Skills

- Leadership
- Communication
- Problem Solving
- Design Thinking
- Team work Feedback
- Facility

Hard skills

- Figma design
- Html
- Css
- Javascript
- React
- Node
- Python
- User flow(Miro)
- Prototype
- User experice
- Video Editing
- Stotytelling

Languages

- Spanisch Native
- English B2-C1
- Germany A2

Diego Francisco Lopez Alvarado

SUMMARY

Hello my name is Diego, I am 27 years old and I am 100% chapin (Guatemalan), I am a very enthusiastic person who loves to have new challenges to be better, I always give 110% giving an excellent job. I am passionate about serving others since I was 14 years old, I have served in various projects and I also like to create impact projects that change lives, I firmly believe that technology can change lives. I graduated from a bootcamp in mexico and I am currently in the process of going deeper into technology.

My goal is that everyone can give their best and that we can learn from each other, and grow together in the process.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apr 2021 - Present

Costumer Representative and Sales Usa and Canada

Royal Carribean Internacional

- Solve problems
- · Create revenue and upselling
- Incresed the sales and service in production.

Dec 2021 - Apr 2022

UX Developer

Geniopay, Lonndon

- · understanding the user.
- Part of the team frontend developmen with HTML, CSS, JAVASCPRIT AND REACT

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021

Development Coordinator

Global U, Usa in Dominic Republic

- Planning with the competent authorities of Infotep.
- · Build of ties between organizations and companies.
- Translate for the team and students.

Jul 2020 - Jan 2021

Assistant of Manager

Shoreline City, Guatemala

- Guided leadership groups and organizing events(Cultivate, Sisterhood) in Guatemala City and Antigua Guatemala. .
- Problem-solving, to find a way to move forward and use critical thinking for each content.
- · Storytelling of the content, recording videos, and editing to production.
- · Increased user engagement; Facebook, Youtube each week to create new content.

Dec 2018 - Oct 2019

Translate Coordinator

Adventures and Mission, Guatemala

- · Leading gruops from United State
- Translate to Spanish to English
- · Coordinator and Admintration English programs
- Teacher of Bible studies.

Feb 2011 - Oct 2014

Volunteer

Iglesia Galilea, Escuela de esperanza

- Translate for teams
- · Building Houses and schools in Escuintla and Sacatepequez
- Leading groups in shows

EDUCATION

May 2021 - Nom2021

Bootcamp in Professional Coding Course

https://devf.la/

Using technologies fast and gorw. React, Javascript, Bootstrap, Css, Html.

2013 - 2019

Law

University of San Carlos

Law, contracts, consulting for commercial legal.

2011 - 2012

Bachelor of Computer Science

Getsemani Institute Tech

Visual basic, pascal, adobe dreamweaver, flash, html,